THOMAS HEADLE

WEB DEVELOPER

(720) 441-3225 TGHeadle@gmail.com - https://github.com/TGHeadle1371 - https://www.linkedin.com/in/thomas-headle/

Summary

Well-versed in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery. Marine Corps Veteran. Bachelor of Science in Environmental Policy and Management. One year of start-up operations and account management experience. Attended a software development coding boot camp through the University of Denver to create web applications on operational efficiency ideas. Equipped with a plethora of skills needed to create environments that bring happiness and purpose to the lives of other users.

Experience

HAPPINESS AMBASSADOR/WAREHOUSE ASSOCIATE/ DRIVER

OH MY GREEN DEC 2017 – present Assist operations manager with day to day tasks; Independently, inventory warehouse, receive products, stock products, and distribute products to sites in an efficient manner.

On-site, provide service to two accounts; maintaining budget, inventory, and positively influencing account manager customer satisfaction on a daily basis.

AFTER-SCHOOL PROGRAM GROUP LEADER

CITY OF LAKEWOOD 2017 – 2018 Provide on-site supervision for program participants, ages 11 to 15 years old, at Creighton and Carmody middle schools. In a professional manner, ensure the health, safety, and well-being of participants at all times.

SQUAD LEADER – COMBAT ENGINEER

UNITED STATES MARINE CORPS 2010 - 2014 Combat Engineer Squad leader in charge of 12 marines health and well-being at all times for duration assigned to billet. Instructed, demonstrated, and ensured proficiency in the various skills needed for pre-deployment, deployment, and post-deployment operations.

Education

Bachelor of Science

PURDUE UNIVERSITY GLOBAL 2014 – 2017 **Environmental Policy and Management**

Cum Laude 3.78

Full-Stack Boot Camp

UNIVERSITY OF DENVER 2017-2018 HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL, MongoDB, Heroku, Git, PHP/Laravel, Writing Tests, Node.js, Express, and overall, the MERN stack.